=Remnants of Gold=
(Adapted from Gu Long's
"Flying Eagle over the Great Land")
(The main characters
in this drama are fictional)
=Episode 7=
Do you kill everyone who comes here?
No need to look.
It's just me.
It's rare for a person
to travel west alone.
It's rare for someone
who almost died here once
to come back.
Am I right?
We were terrified last time, too.
Shiquan Fort was abandoned first,
and now Lieyang Well
is almost abandoned, too.
Once the roads
heading west are deserted,
no one will come
looking for gold anymore.
Am I right?
How should I address you?
Yu Hou.
Sir,
what are you looking for?
I was careless last time.
I didn't investigate you and your son.
Seventeen,
go outside and enjoy the sun.
You poisoned the feed.
What poison in the feed?
So this is what
guardians of the gold look like.
What are we supposed to look like?
Where are
the 300,000 taels of gold buried?
I could ask your son instead.
Seventeen,
go somewhere further
to enjoy the sun.
How far?
Across the street.
Seventeen,
go.
You came here seeking death.
It's easy for me to kill you.
No need for poison.
Really?
I dare to kill you,
but you don't dare to kill me.
Because you want the gold.
When people desire something,
they have a weakness.
Your son out on the street...
Isn't he your weakness?
People like us
shouldn't have loved ones!
How many
guardians of the gold
like you are there?
Gold is heavier than life, isn't it?
You still don't dare to kill me.
Most people in this world are fools,
never understanding it until they die!
Fine.
Then I will kill you.
Let go of me!
♪Are climbing the mountain♪
♪A young girl♪
♪Waves her hand♪
♪I should go over, right?♪
♪But the door is locked♪
♪Should I stay away?♪
♪But my heart is itching♪
Bancha.
Seventeen.
How are you doing?
Are they your new women?
You rascal,
don't talk nonsense.
When have I ever had a woman?
Then who are they?
Pretty ladies.
Women's clothes?
The last time you reached this place,
Lieyang Well became deserted.
Drain
all of your blood later.
Your son is outside.
Are you really making him
watch you kill someone?
My son is across the street.
Unless I tell him to come back,
he won't come back.
He's not very bright.
Pretty ladies, pretty ladies.
There are pretty ladies.
Pretty ladies.
♪Two mountain goats♪
♪Are climbing the mountain♪
♪Should I go over?♪
♪A little girl♪
♪Looks so pretty♪
♪Should I go over?♪
Two pretty ladies are outside.
♪But the door is locked♪
♪Should I stay away?♪
The two pretty ladies
are on the street.
♪But my heart is itching♪
You go to the street, too.
Go.
What are you doing?
I'm just getting ready
to draw a bucket of water.
♪Should I go over?♪
♪But the door is locked♪
Lieyang Well is the only spring here.
What will we do if it gets contaminated?
It won't get contaminated.
I was just preparing to pull him up,
bleed him dry,
carry him out, and bury him.
Does it have to be like this?
When you passed by here heading east,
you said you'd buy me highland
barley liquor when you returned.
Where's the liquor?
There's someone in this well
who needs to be pulled up and bled dry,
yet you're talking to me
about highland barley liquor?
You're Bancha, the man who never lies.
The liquor is gone.
Then you lied.
The guardians of the gold are here.
Where?
This is enchanting grass
of the Western Regions.
Someone specifically
transplanted it here.
The first-year tender leaves are edible,
and the seeds can be
ground into medicine.
It's recorded in old formulas
from the Yuan Dynasty.
They look like they're alive.
They're dead now.
They pull all their roots
out of the soil,
roll into a ball,
and roll with the wind.
The enchanting grass here
has been dead for over ten years.
Are they toxic now?
If horses eat them
and then encounter water,
people will start killing
each other within ten steps.
Was it this grass that was used
for the guardians of the gold's
poison feed?
Exposing them directly to water
makes the toxicity even stronger.
Even I would have to
take the antidote first.
But once submerged in water,
the toxicity dissipates immediately.
This street is 93 meters long.
Light one stick every 10 meters.
Tie Futu will arrive in 15 minutes.
How do you know that, Luyao?
We set out before dawn
just to stay ahead.
With the eagles flying
west along the way,
pushing back by 15 minutes,
that would be them.
What incense is this?
Water incense.
Fifteen minutes later,
the moisture will thicken,
and the whole street
will be covered in water mist.
Pretty ladies.
Pretty ladies!
The kid called me "pretty lady".
Let's go over?
When Tie Futu and the others get here,
they'll start killing each other, right?
Just like my father and brothers did.
You stay here.
When the moisture rises,
keep this in your mouth.
Luyao.
Pretty lady.
Luyao!
Could you
give me one more pill?
For Fang?
How are you going
to give it to him then?
I'll risk my life to give it to him.
If someone drowns in there,
I'll never drink
from Lieyang Well again.
Who is the woman that came with you?
Before, she was looking
for the guardians of the gold.
Now, someone else
is having her look for them.
Let's bleed her dry
and bury her together with him.
Hey,
don't touch her.
So,
is she really your lady?
I'm not like you.
Fifteen years ago,
you hid it from everyone,
fell in love with a woman,
and had a son with her.
People like us
aren't allowed to have families.
It's not like you don't know that.
Did you tell her everything?
Tell her what?
About who we are
and where the gold is buried.
Can I ask you a few questions?
Or maybe
just one question?
Do you really have to ask?
You don't have to answer.
That way, it won't count as lying.
Do you like this place?
She didn't ask,
so I didn't say.
What if she asks?
If she asks, I'll just say.
I am Bancha, who doesn't lie.
Who else did you tell before?
I'll tell anyone who asks.
And kill them once I do.
The Zhang lady didn't ask,
so I won't hurt her.
You aren't allowed to touch her, either.
Actually, I think she knows everything.
She's a particularly clever lady.
She's the Zhang lady.
What are you doing?
Creating fog on this street.
That's impossible.
Go away.
Don't let the mist touch you.
Why?
Get far away.
Get lost!
I told you to get lost!
The further, the better!
Or I'll kill you!
What are you doing?
I'm going to bleed him.
He isn't dead yet.
Once I bleed him, he will be.
Bancha,
can you ask your friend
to wait a moment?
How
did you know he's my friend?
He's one of the guardians of the gold,
so he is your friend.
See that?
She really knows everything.
It's not hard to guess.
My father and brothers
died from poison in the feed.
The poison is made from
enchanting grass of the Western Regions.
Lieyang Well is full
of enchanting grass,
and you are the only ones
killing people here.
This man
is looking for gold.
I didn't kill your father and brothers.
But the poison is yours.
I said I didn't kill
your father and brothers.
The poison is yours,
isn't it?
It is mine.
But who poisoned
your father and brothers?
The poisoner will be here in 15 minutes.
Who?
Who used my poison to kill people?
Tie Futu,
the ruthless killer
from the Northwest Great Desert.
You knew all this?
Why didn't you say anything?
You didn't ask.
How should I know you wanted to know?
What did I say?
This lady knows everything.
I want to ask him a few questions.
Kill him after I'm done.
Han Jade.
Eight-Cut Wengzhong.
Am I right?
Why do you like these things?
Because they're expensive.
Being with them keeps my mind at ease.
Are you uneasy now?
My mind is made up.
I'm not uneasy anymore.
I've thrown away
the bell you gave me.
Are you done asking?
My men
will arrive at Lieyang Well very soon.
You are about to die.
What's there to regret about dying?
What's the point of gold
once you're dead?
What's the point of living?
If evil thoughts harbor in your mind,
you'll act on them anyway.
Either die,
or die after getting rich.
You die in the end anyway.
How did you turn out like this?
I've always been like this.
You knew long ago
that the guardians of the gold
were at Lieyang Well, right?
Why did you keep having Fang follow me?
So you knew it.
Fang's spear
was in the cloth bundle
in your room all along.
That spear is very costly, too.
I gave him the spear
so he'd obey your orders
and protect your life.
Move aside!
I still have a few
more questions to ask.
Who do you think you are?
I just want to ask him a few questions.
Just let her ask.
We can listen up.
You dense villain.
Tie Futu
sent my family an escort order
and poisoned them.
You knew beforehand.
Sorry,
I wanted the gold.
Expenses are high in the south.
Three hundred thousand taels
of gold are a lot.
The Zhang Escort Agency is
under your jurisdiction in Liangzhou.
You're the chief official of Liangzhou.
Colluding with bandits
to murder and rob...
Does the Commander-in-Chief
know you're doing this?
Does he know?
You said the General
was like a father and brother to you.
So that's how it is.
It was General
who wanted the 300,000 taels of gold.
No.
So it was
the Commander-in-Chief of Gansu
who ordered you and Tie Futu
to murder and rob.
That's impossible.
Do you want to die, too?
I told you long ago
that you're too bloodthirsty.
I won't rest easy
until everyone is dead!
It's only because you raised a son
that you can't let anything go.
What choice do I have?
I already have a son.
What else can I do?
Is the mist poisonous?
It's not poisonous.
It's just water vapor.
To be safe,
we still shouldn't cross.
Guys,
cover your mouths.
Put the guy
up front.
Hold on to him.
Don't let him run.
If you hadn't taken it upon yourself
to poison both groups from Lieyang Well
and Shiquan Fort,
would things have come to this?
What choice did I have?
They wanted the gold!
Fang!
It's the Zhang lady.
Let me ask you one more time.
You knew all along
about the murder of
my father and brothers?
Yes.
Did General order you to do this?
I wanted to kill your family.
It has nothing to do with him.
You're not that kind of person.
What kind of person am I then?
Let's part ways here.
Let's settle everything
once and for all.
You've never killed anyone before.
How will you
get revenge like this?
Kill me.
Fang!
It's me, Pingping.
Let them kill you then.
Haven't enough people looked
for the gold over these 30 years?
Just let them search.
You kill whoever wants to look?
Are you crazy?
He's run off,
and you're still fighting? You fool.
It's me, Pingping.
Pingping...
Hurry.
Open your mouth.
Their mouths were covered.
Where did the feed poison come from?
It's from the mist and the things
on the ground, I think.
Why didn't you realize this earlier?
We've never seen
anything like this before.
Why didn't you go there?
Didn't you stay behind, too?
We gave you 100 taels of gold.
You ought to do something for it, right?
What about my men?
It's too late for them.
We don't have that much antidote.
Antidote?
What kind of antidote is it?
Universal Antidote.
Take him to the main house.
(Preview of the Next Episode)
If you want to die,
I'll send you on your way!
Kill this jerk!
- Kill him!
Where is the gold?
Keep heading west.
Once you pass Shiquan Fort,
my son and I will take you there.
=Remnants of Gold=